[
  {
    "front": "Returns the number of nodes in the collection",
    "back": "length"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the node at the specified index in a node list",
    "back": "item()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the number of nodes in the collection",
    "back": "length"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the specified node (by name)",
    "back": "getNamedItem()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the node at the specified index in the namedNodeMap",
    "back": "item()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Removes the specified node (by name)",
    "back": "removeNamedItem()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets the specified node (by name)",
    "back": "setNamedItem()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the specified node (by name and namespace)",
    "back": "getNamedItemNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Removes the specified node (by name and namespace)",
    "back": "removeNamedItemNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets the specified node (by name and namespace)",
    "back": "setNamedItemNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the Document Type Declaration associated with the document",
    "back": "doctype"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the Document Element of the document (the HTML element)",
    "back": "documentElement"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets or returns the location of the document",
    "back": "documentURI"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the DOMImplementation object that handles this document",
    "back": "implementation"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the encoding, character set, used for the document",
    "back": "inputEncoding"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the XML encoding of the XML document",
    "back": "xmlEncoding"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets or returns the XML version of the XML document",
    "back": "xmlVersion"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the configuration used when normalizeDocument() is invoked",
    "back": "domConfig"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates an attribute node",
    "back": "createAttribute()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates a CDATA node with the specified text. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "createCDATASection()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates a Comment node with the specified text",
    "back": "createComment()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates an empty DocumentFragment node",
    "back": "createDocumentFragment()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates an Element node",
    "back": "createElement()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates an EntityReference node. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "createEntityReference()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates a Text node",
    "back": "createTextNode()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the element that has the ID attribute with the specified value",
    "back": "getElementById()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns a NodeList containing all elements with the specified tagname",
    "back": "getElementsByTagName()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns a list of elements with a given name in the (X)HTML document.",
    "back": "getElementsByName()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns a NodeList containing all elements that match the specified CSS selector",
    "back": "querySelectorAll()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the first element matching the specified CSS selector",
    "back": "querySelector()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns a NodeList containing all elements with the specified namespaceURI and tagname",
    "back": "getElementsByTagNameNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Imports a node from another document",
    "back": "importNode()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Adopts a node from another document to this document. Returns the adopted node",
    "back": "adoptNode(node)"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates an attribute with the specified name and namspaceURI",
    "back": "createAttributeNS(URI,name)"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates an element with the specified namespace",
    "back": "createElementNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Creates an EntityReference node. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "createProcessingInstruction()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Removes empty Text nodes, and joins adjacent nodes",
    "back": "normalizeDocument()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the tag name of the element",
    "back": "tagName"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the type information of the element.",
    "back": "schemaTypeInfo"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the specified attribute value",
    "back": "getAttribute()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the specified attribute value, with the specified namespace. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "getAttributeNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the specified attribute node",
    "back": "getAttributeNode()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the specified attribute node, with the specified namespace. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "getAttributeNodeNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns a collection of all child elements with the specified tagname",
    "back": "getElementsByTagName()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns a collection of all child elements with the specified tagname and namespace. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "getElementsByTagNameNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns true if the element has the specified attribute, otherwise it returns false",
    "back": "hasAttribute()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns true if the element has the specified attribute, with the specified namespace, otherwise it returns false. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "hasAttributeNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Removes the specified attribute",
    "back": "removeAttribute()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Removes the attribute with the specified name and namespace. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "removeAttributeNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Removes the specified attribute node, and returns the removed node",
    "back": "removeAttributeNode()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets or changes the specified attribute, to the specified value",
    "back": "setAttribute()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets or changes the specified attribute, with the specified namespace, to the specified value. For XML DOM only",
    "back": "setAttributeNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets or changes the specified attribute node",
    "back": "setAttributeNode()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets or changes the specified attribute node",
    "back": "setAttributeNodeNS()"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns ",
    "back": "isId"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the name of the attribute",
    "back": "name"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the element this attribute belongs to",
    "back": "ownerElement"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns ",
    "back": "specified"
  },
  {
    "front": "Sets or returns the value of the attribute",
    "back": "value"
  },
  {
    "front": "Returns the type information of the attribute",
    "back": "schemaTypeInfo"
  }
]
